Thompson, Sanford E. Papers 5615
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series V. FREDERICK W. TAYLOR FILES 1892-1915
  - Sub-Series 3. B. Publications
    - "Bulletin of the Taylor Society" (Box 16, Folder 15-17)
      Vol. 10, #6; Vol. 11, #2-5; Vol. 12, #1,6; Vol. 13, #1,3,5
    - Misc. & publications. "Classification for Filing Correspondence Relating to Taylor System and Taylor System Appliances" (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - F.W. Taylor - Miscellaneous and Publications. "A Collection of Original Frederick W. Taylor Documents", 1978 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Professional Papers - Publications. "Industrial Management" by Taylor & Morris Cooke, 1909 (Box 17, Folder 1-10)
    - Miscellaneous and publications. Photograph of F.W. Taylor (Box 17, Folder 11)